Okay, so let's do some math.
我们来做一点计算
Let's assign to each data point an initial weight of one.
假设每个数据点的初始权重相同为 1
Now, let's fit our first learner.
现在 我们先拟合第一个学习器
Before, we wanted to minimize the number of errors.
之前我们需要最大程度地减少错误数量
Now, we want to minimize the sum of weights of the incorrectly classified points which,
现在我们只要把误分类的点的权重和降到最小值
as of now, is the same.
二者其实是一样的
So, here is the model.
在这个模型中
If we add the weights of the correctly classified points,
如果我们把正确分类的点的权重相加
we get a seven,
结果是 7
and three for the incorrectly classified points.
而误分类点的权重和是 3
So, let's weight the incorrectly classified points a bit more.
我们再进一步为这些误分类的点赋予权重
How much? Well, let's make it enough to have this model be a 50-50 model.
赋予多少权重呢？条件是要使得该模型成为一个 50:50 的模型
So if we take these three points and weight them by
所以 如果我们筛选出这三个点 然后给他们赋予三分之七的权重
a factor of seven over three, or 2.33,
也就是 2.33
then our model now has seven as the sum
那该模型现在正确分类的点的权重和
of the weights of the correctly classified points,
即为 7
and also seven as the sum of the weights of the incorrectly classified points.
误分类的点的权重和同样是 7
So, this model now is lame, and we need a second one.
这个模型是站不住脚的 我们需要第二个模型
And our second model will be this one,
我们需要的第二个模型
which fits the newly weighted data best.
要最大化的匹配这些新的权重值
For this one, we can see that if we add the weights on the correctly classified points,
在这个模型中 如果我们把正确分类的点的权重相加
we get 11, and for the incorrectly classified ones, we get three again.
所得结果为 11 误分类的点的权重和是 3
So, let's weigh the incorrectly classified points.
所以我们再一次为误分类的点赋予权重
By how much? Well, enough to make this model a 50-50 model again.
赋予多少呢？同样 条件是要使得该模型成为 50:50 的模型
Notice that if we weigh these three errors,
注意如果我赋予这三个错误
each one by a factor of 11 over three,
三分之十一的权重 也就是 3.66
or 3.66, now the sum of the weights of the incorrectly classified points is 11.
那么新得到的这些误分类的点的权重和就是11
So, our model is just a 50-50 model again. That's lame.
这个模型还是一个 50:50 的模型 同样站不住脚
Let's fit a third model in this newly weighted data.
让我们用这些新的权值来拟合第三个模型
And here's our third model.
这就是第三个模型
Now what is the added weight of the correctly classified points?
那么正确分类的点的权重和是多少呢？
Now it's 19, and still three for the incorrect ones.
答案是 19 而误分类的点的权重和依然是3
We can keep this going, but let's stop.
这个流程可以继续进行下去 但我们先停在这里
We have built three models.
我们已经建立了三个模型
And here are the three models,
分别是这三个模型
or weak learners, that we built.
或者叫三个弱学习器
In the next video, we will learn how to combine them.
下一个视频中 我们来学习如何把它们集成到一起